Good mornin'.
What you got? Let me see this.
Oh. Whoosh.
Yeah. What's that? Boop boop.
What do you think?
Wah!
What's that necklace for?
-Hello!
-Good morning, Meme.
Morning, Jamie.
Ah!
You hand over that baby to me
right this minute.
-Who's that?
-Who's my heart?
Who's that?
-Aww.
-Oh.
That's it, come to Meme.
Thank you for doing this, Meme.
Aww aww.
That's a grumpy baby.
Oh! One more goodbye, yeah?
You gonna stay
with Meme today, yeah?
Yeah.
Be good. Be a good girl.
You all right
staying the night?
Aww... oh! 'Course, darlin'.
Nothing would make me happier.
Oh, my!
-Papas leavin'.
-I'll be back today.
Daddy will be back.
He'll be back.
-Thank you, Meme.
-He'll be back.
All right, so there I was.
Day two, in the sandbox.
In a convoy, on the 81st.
I'm sittin' up top,
at the gunner seat.
Fucking hearts beating
through my chest 'cause I...
I heard it's the most dangerous
stretch of road in the country.
Fuck yeah, it is.
What could go wrong?
So we're cruising along.
All of a sudden,
I see this fucking Hajji
on the side of the road.
And he's going to town
-on a fuckin donkey--
-He's got--
Hang on a minute!
A fucking donkey?
Bro, he's got
his little Hajji dress
hiked up over his shoulders
bangin' away.
-How do you even do that?
-Super fucking weird, right?
I even said somethin' to Gunny
about it but he shrugs it off.
So we don't get another
six klicks down the road,
I see another fucking Alibaba
off in the distance
ridin' one of his own
behind this broken down Humvee.
What, like another donkey
in the butthole?
So what happened next?
More of the same.
I must've seen like
fuckin' four more pairs of 'em.
Gettin' after it on the way back
to the farm. right?
What?
So... uh...
It gets worse.
All right, so we get back
to the motor pool
and I see this old dirty bastard
about yay high,
with a wooden leg
sittin' on the hood
of the major's Humvee,
jerkin' off.
-You're kidding.
-What?
-Yeah--
-How the fuck do you
even get in there?
So Gunny looks up to me,
can see how fuckin' rattled
I am, right?
Then he asks me what
my malfunction is.
I mean, my malfunction,
I'm telling you, the whole
fucking way here I'm seeing
dudes bangin' donkeys
on the side of the road.
There's this guy
with a wooden leg
beatin' off in the motor pool
in broad daylight
and you know what he says to me?
What'd he say?
"Marine, you can't expect a guy
with a wooden leg
to catch a fucking donkey."
Crazy motherfucker.
Jesus Christ.
We here.
What's your problem?
Why you poutin'?
Bitch, I ain't fuckin' poutin'.
-Yeah, you are.
-Fuck you.
Let's rock and roll.
I know the transfer took
a little bit longer
than we wanted,
but we appreciate your business
and we appreciate your trust.
Everybody freeze!
Don't you fuckin' move!
- Hands away from
the weapons, all.
-Nah nah nah nah nah.
-Think it through.
Everybody fuckin' relax.
You heard him.
Don't fuckin' move.
-Stop!
-Shut up!
All right, you heard the man.
Let's start with
you three ladies right there.
Hands laced on top of your head.
Back away from the counter.
Let's go.
Get against the fucking wall.
Everyone else, on the floor!
Eyes on the fucking floor, pal.
Get on the floor, bitch!
-Whoa!
-Guys, just relax! All right?
Heads down. Eyes down.
This ain't worth dying for.
Give me the fucking key.
Give me the fucking key!
Smart!
No no no no no!
-Ah ah!
-Oh, God! Oh, my--!
-Ah!
-Shut the fuck up,
or your fucking thumb's next.
Let's go. I need the code.
Ah! Three, 17, 77.
Look at my fucking eyes,
if that's a panic code...
he's gonna cut off a lot more
than your fucking thumb.
You understand me?
One, 23, seven, nine.
You, motha--
Shut the fuck up!
We're in!
- Uh-uh-uh.
- Whoa!
Bro, we're out of clock.
Clear!
Now!
Ah!
Cops at rear!
-Move back!
-Wait!
All clear! All clear!
Wait for it! Wait for it!
Contacts left!
Move!
Let it go! Hey!
We said to... only.
Motherfuck!
Move back! Move--
Moving.
-Move!
-Move it!
Contact right!
-Hey! Spread out, to your left!
-Move!
Moving!
That's it.
Reloading!
Move!
-Oh!
-Moving!
Back there!
Move!
Moving!
We're clear!
Code, move!
Moving!
Reloading!
-Move!
-Moving!
We're clear!
Hey! Wait out on me,
wait out on me! Move!
-Moving!
-Wait up!
Move!
Move! Move!
-Fuck! Shit!
-Come on!
-Ah!
-Hey!
What the fuck
are you doing, man?
Let's go.
Come on! Let's go.
Keep your fuckin' head down,
all right?
All right, come on.
Go walk!
Get some! Get some! Get some!
Out of the car!
Put your head down!
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Get the fuck in, Vic!
-Let's fuckin' go!
-Drive!
Left, left!
Fuck!
Back, back, back!
Come on, motherfuckers.
Come on...
Turn here! Here!
Come on, come on!
- Yo, get down!
- Get the fuck down!
Dispatch,
we have multiple officers down
at first National Bank,
South Conti and Calhoun.
Requesting air meds for
location, ASAP.
Citywide, all units respond.
-  One, O, eight.
- Multiple officers down.
EMS, Code three.
All units,
suspect vehicle is a 90s model,
light blue, wood paneled,
Chevy station wagon.
Be advised,
suspects are armed.
with fully automatic weapons.
Notified J.P., Saint Bernard,
Saint Tammany,
and State Police.
Requesting shutdown
of all routes out of the city.
including the Crescent City
Connection,
Causeway, the Twin Span,
and all routes headed
westbound.
-Gonna say nothing?
-What you want me to say?
What the fuck was that?
FBI robbery task force.
No shit.
-How'd they know?
-Someone ratted us.
Who?
We gotta wash this money.
Make sure our exit's
not burning,
and get the fuck out.
Fast.
Where we gonna run?
This is gonna
make national news, Mick.
We're fucking cop killers now.
The choice is what?
You hear anybody yell,
"Don't move, you're under
arrest"? No, you didn't.
They were there
to fucking murder us,
and I ain't got no regrets.
We left, fucking,
three of our brothers
in the fucking street!
They made their choices.
Two, I've already given
my statement to your paid men.
-Gentlemen!
-You're probably not--
Pace.
So you're the one in charge
of this shit show.
That's Special Agent
Frank Ross.
Where the fuck were you,
Special Agent?
I just got off a plane from
D.C. ten minutes ago.
I've got six dead officers
and another one in critical
because of your team's
cowboy shit.
I understand, Lieutenant.
I do.
It went bad
and we're here.
We've gotta move past that now,
so we can focus
on catching these guys.
"Catch 'em."
It's New Orleans, Special Agent.
We're gonna bury
these motherfuckers.
Do your thing,
but don't go fucking shit
on my crime scene.
Remember,
this is homicide first,
robbery second.
I understand you're upset.
Emotional.
You have every reason to be...
But if you ever sling
foul language at me again,
it will be your last.
Understand?
So, where we at on lockdown?
In motion, boss.
Mayor's given us the keys.
There are checkpoints
everywhere.
, the causeway,
all the ports,
highways, bridges, roads
-heading out the city.
-Marinas?
Yes, sir. Everything.
All right, all right.
I want C.R.T. teams
and every precinct standing by.
-So, what exactly happened?
-I got a call from my buddy
in Vice.
Said he hooked a guy yesterday,
on some sort of statutory shit.
Some nobody, Edwin Smalls.
That cyber security geek is
looking at five to seven years
in Angola.
Folded like a lawn-chair.
They literally called us
ten minutes
before the crew hit the place.
I tried to phone you,
but I couldn't reach you.
So... I made the call.
So, tell me why we couldn't
take 'em at the van.
Well, the block car
was in motion,
and we were pushin' up.
Crew came out heavy
like before, five and a driver.
Body armor, ballistics, masks,
all automatic stuff...
And then, fender bender
right in front of us,
as we were moving in.
Boris Karloff over there,
at the front door,
came up on his sights.
I beat him to the punch.
It was on.
Nico took out the driver
of the van.
Swat got the mummy over there
at the dumpster.
So, I hear you winged a fourth.
You sure you hit him?
Oh, I hit meat.
I heard the man howl.
And, I tell ya,
there ain't no way he makes it
through the night without
some serious medical attention.
These guys are smart,
they're way too ruthless.
Find out if there are any
doctors who've come up missing.
Look into... vet offices,
plastic surgeons,
anyone who can handle trauma.
On it.
You know how you've been saying
you thought these guys
were ex-military.
-Yeah
-Yeah, well, you're right.
We had them pinned down.
and guess what those assholes
go and do?
-Attack the ambush.
-Exactly.
Wasn't till they realized
they were boxed in
that they started to fall back.
And the ranger peeled
all the way down the fence
and out.
-Ranger peel?
-Yeah.
Move, moving, covering,
all at high speed shit.
I gotta tell you,
I haven't seen that live
since Somalia.
-Go on.
-They jacked some kid
for his station wagon.
Mark unit ran him down,
but that just turned
into an ambush.
at the switch car,
'bout, uh, six blocks over.
All right. Get eyes out.
We're looking for something big.
You know, something that
can carry all of them,
something with power.
We're talkin' a large SUV,
three-by-three, one ton.
-Copy that.
-Yeah.
Tell me about this van.
Stole it. Three days,
out of Chalmette.
-Nico
-Yes, sir.
Who do we have over here?
Bank tellers, managers
en route to University Medical.
Heard he put up a fight,
and they tuned him up
pretty good.
-Pssh... Not smart.
-No, sir.
Hi. Now,
just one moment.
Detective, do you mind
if I ask your witnesses
a couple questions?
Seriously? I got a kid I was
supposed to pick up hours ago.
-Go for it. I'm done.
-Thank you. Ladies...
My name is Special Agent
Frank Ross.
-Look... we just wanna go home.
-I understand. I do.
I just need
a moment of your time.
Do you remember anything...
Anything specific about
the gunman who did this?
-Two of 'em were Y'at.
-Y'at?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry -I don't
know what a Y'at is--
Metro locals. That Brooklyn
accent that you think
you've been hearing around town?
It ain't. That's a thing
we call Y'at.
Okay. All right. Uh...
Which ones were Y'ats?
The vampire and wolf.
Okay. Thank you, thank you.
That's very, very helpful.
Thank you very much.
Ma'am, what about you?
Did you see anything?
Do you remember anything?
Ma'am?
Guns. All I saw was guns.
I mainly just kept my head down.
I didn't wanna...
make eye contact.
That was smart.
That was very smart.
Okay, just breathe...
It's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
Ex... excuse me, one moment.
Dad, where are you?
I've been waiting forever.
You're not coming, are you?
Tomorrow morning
Works always first, right?
-I should've known--
-Frank, I just got word...
car fire on Chapitoulas.
Ladies...
Thank you, thank you.
Please don't hesitate to call
Detective here,
if you remember
anything at all. Okay?
All right?
Thank you all again.
-Thanks, Agent Ross.
-Yeah.
Get their details.
Run 'em all through local,
state, NCIC...
-Will do.
-You drive.
-Who the f--
-Yo, Bill, open the door man.
-Whoa whoa whoa whoa!
Bro...
-Yo, open the door, Bill.
Whoa whoa whoa!
You can't bring him in here!
Jeremy, this ain't how it works!
Tell me, motherfucker,
how's it work?
How's it fucking work?
- Thought you'd rat us out,
didn't you?
-Open your eyes,
I want you to see this.
-Hey, no no no.
Come on,
he's as fucked as we are.
No no no, he fucking knew.
He fucking knew.
You're the only one
who fuckin' knew.
No, wrong.
Smalls knew.
What?
When it hit the news,
I knew-- I made a call.
-NOPD picked him up
yesterday.
Fuck.
-We need another way out.
-Smalls didn't know
nothing about it.
We don't know what the fuck he
knew, what he told him...
-Hey, we need to wash
that shit ASAP.
-No can do.
My guy's out.
Too much blood on it.
-Blue blood.
-Oh, fuck that, fuck that.
Tell him we'll give him
another bu--
ten percent.
He's out!
I don't care if you give him
100 percent!
Jamie...
It's too much heat.
There's fucking
cash in a bag, right?
Nobody's gonna fucking
clean that for us?
Yeah...
The one guy I can dig up
that might be able to
move that much weight...
That's Nussy.
And, boys,
the hit won't be light,
Cause he's gonna take,
forty, fifty percent...
minimum.
I mean, it is what it is, right?
Fuck it. Make the fucking call.
Yes, sir.
Put your fucking guns down.
What the fuck!
-Here we go-
Pearl, right?
-What the fuck are you doin'?
-Fuck... you!
You piece of shit.
You fucking coward.
-Handle your business,
little bro--
-You fucking scum!
I ain't got fucking time
for this--
Fuck, you promised me, Jamie,
shit. You promised me--
Get the fuck out of here.
I'm gonna fucking kill you.
I'm gonna kill you.
What are you doin'?!
That psycho motherfucker
just killed us.
Fuck! What was I thinking,
Jamie?
We should've known better!
We should've known better.
- Fuck, Jamie!
- Hey.
Joan! Joan!
The surgery was paid for.
-Jamie, we had everything.
Jamie, everything is gone now.
-Shh... shh.
-Stop.
-What... what?
- What?
- Come here.
Listen. Hey... We're gonna
get through this, okay?
All right?
How?
How? How do we get through this?
I'm workin' on it.
All right?
But you can't be here!
We had a plan. You go home.
You act like
everything is normal.
You can't be around these guys,
all right?
You need to listen to me.
The FBI's on you.
They talk to you?
Yeah, yeah. They were at
the bank for, like, hours.
They talked to everybody.
They're looking for guys
from the neighborhood.
They're gonna find you, Jamie.
And... and...
Listen... what if we just left.
-What if we left right now...
and you came with me right now?
-Hey... Shh--
-And we go get Joannie--
-Stop! Stop!
And we get the fuck out of here.
You come with me...
There's one thing
that's important. You go home.
That's it.
Let me work!
All right?
You trust me?
You know I do.
I can't have this.
You gotta get him out of here.
Shut the door! Shut the door!
Jamie, he's gotta go!
Where the fuck
am I gonna take him, Bill?
Let's take him to Clarence.
We ain't takin' him
to fucking Clarence's.
Dump him at the E.R.
and hope for the best.
-Take him to--
-Take him to fucking Clarence.
I'm coming with.
-What?
-Yeah.
No you're fucking going home.
We just talked about this.
I ain't leavin' you here
with this fucking psychopath.
-Ava.
-No way! I'm not going home!
You know what?
That's a great idea.
Cops ain't looking
for no pretty brunette
from the Channel.
Here! You drive!
I'm not leaving your side
till this is over with.
You fuck us...and I will be back
to murder you where you stand.
We clear?
We're clear.
The surviving assailants
are believed to have made off
with over one point five
million dollars.
The New Orleans Police
Department,
in conjunction with the FBI's
elite robbery task force unit
have begun
an extensive manhunt.
Setting up roadblocks
and checkpoints.
Effectively shutting down
all access points
both in and out of the city.
If you, or anyone you know,
has any information on
the whereabouts
of these fugitives,
the New Orleans Police
Department asks that
you contact them immediately.
But do not approach.
The assailants are considered
armed and extremely dangerous.
Now, let's go to George,
who's standing by
at University Medical,
- awaiting an update
on the state,
of the officers wounded
in today's heinous attack.
- Yo
- Hank,
the situation at the hospital
-Who's this?
- at the hospital
is extremely grim.
-Oh, yeah.
- And with good reason.
-Today's tragic events--
-Yo, Nussy.
marked the deadliest incident--
Got some fool on the line
that says you knows him.
Told me to tell ya,
he's willing to chat.
The Jet,
what you want?
Some arriving, still unaware.
of whether their loved ones
Yeah, I'm lookin' at that shit
right now.
These some straight up
mad motherfuckers,
right here.
Oh, yeah? Enlighten me.
It's a good location
to dump a car.
You got 90 only seconds away,
and the Irish Channel
to get lost in, right there.
So, what's next?
We flex this. Okay?
So what do we know?
Three shooters. One's hurtin'.
Two of 'em are
probably local boys.
All ex-military.
Not just military...
these guys are gunfighters.
We're lookin' for vets
with trigger time
in the sandbox.
I'll get Jean
to reach out to DOD.
-And I'll pull Jefferson
and Orleans' barrage.
-Good.
So what exactly was the take?
Walked out with three mil,
got away with one point five.
What was a bank in East Calhoun
doing with that much cash?
They just took over
the temp headquarters branch,
because the CBD location
was going through a remodel.
And today's Thursday.
So, they were carrying
heavy prepping' for distribution
to all the other branches.
Cover all those
Friday payroll checks.
And, how do they know all this?
That's our job.
You mentioned earlier,
an Edwin Smalls...
That's right. The rat.
Smalls gave them intel
and boards.
What kind of boards?
Some high-end, custom stuff,
designed to trigger
the alarm system
-to shut itself off 15 minutes
before the crew hit the place.
-Okay.
I followed up on that
with the bank's security firm.
They told me that they found
two odd, custom boards
installed in the master CPU.
They're polygraphing
the entire staff as we speak.
So if Smalls hadn't talked,
they'd have gotten away clean?
Hundred percent.
Hmm...
I wanna speak to this nobody.
This Mr. Edwin Smalls.
Holy shit.
Get the fuck out of here.
We need you.
I got you. Come on!
Get the hell in here! Quick!
Put him over here.
Sorry 'bout the mess, man.
I was about to
clean this shit up.
Put him right here.
- Bullet hit him
under his armpit.
-His right armpit.
-His other right armpit,
Clarence!
-Where the fucking blood is!
-Would you just chill out, man?!
You got me so fucking rattled,
I can't even think straight!
I got this.
Just let me do my thing!
Clarence! Who's that?
- Who the fuck is that?
- Who you got in there?
Ma! It's the pie guy.
He's just droppin' off a
pepperoni.
But I hate pepperoni!
Yeah, I know!
It's not for you! It's for me.
You said you didn't want any.
-That ain't no pie guy!
-Mom, just relax, okay?
I'll be there in a bit
to rub your feet.
- Really?
- I promise, Ma!
Just watch your program,
and I'll be in there
before it's over.
-Yo, what the fuck
are you doin'?
-I--I--I need my bag.
-What bag?
-It's a medical bag.
It's green. It's about this big.
-This it?
-That's it. Toss it here.
Now, everybody
just give me my space,
and let me do my thing.
-It's Bill.
-Take it. I got it.
-You got this?
-Yeah, I got it. Go go go go go.
Hey, what's up?
What you got?
He's down, but it's a shit deal.
Thirty cents on the dollar.
Fuck, that's seventy percent.
I know, but it's one of those
take-it-or-leave-it situations.
Your call.
-All right.
-How's the bleeding?
Not good.
So how we gonna do this?
This dude has lost
a shit ton of blood.
My guess is the bullet
bounced off his shoulders,
start gettin' down
to his stomach.
His abdomen is distended,
and he's got a G.I. bleed.
I ain't got time for this, Bro.
Well, I don't know
what to tell you, bro!
I'm a corpsman, man,
not a surgeon.
Without real trauma care,
and even then-- I don't know!
Ain't gonna happen,
can't happen.
You make it go easy for him.
Take it!
What's goin' on?
Yeah, it's all good.
I--I did my thing.
And, uh, he's in rough shape,
but the bleeding stopped.
He just needs some time to rest.
Well, we ain't got time
for no rest.
You gotta get him fixed up,
ASAP.
Get him over to Bill's house.
He can rest when we get there.
-What's Bill have to say?
-Got a deal.
-Twenty minutes
and we will know. You hear me?
-Yeah.
-Let's move. Let's go.
Hey...
Thank you.
-Yeah, man.
-Take care of him.
Look... as soon as
we're done with this,
I'm gonna drop you off
at St. Charles.
You're gonna
take the street car home.
When are you comin' home?
I don't know.
-So this is it?
-No, it's not it.
All right? As soon as
the heat dies down,
I'mma send for you and Joan.
Jamie...
You ain't never gonna
send for us.
If you make it out of this,
and that's--that's a big if...
You're gonna be running
for the rest of your life.
I got a plan.
-What plan?
-Bolivia--
-Let me explain--
-Bolivia?
-Listen to me. Listen to me.
-Jamie, I don't even know--
-I don't even know,
where the fuck that is, Jamie--
-Listen--
It's in South America,
and there's this big lake
down there,
Massive.
Right on the Bolivian,
Peruvian line.
Right there on the border,
surrounded
by the Andes Mountains.
And, in the middle of
this big lake,
there's this little island
called Isla de Sol.
There's no cars,
no roads,
Just fishermen and farmers.
All right? You, me, and Joan
could start a life there.
Just the three of us together?
Jamie...
-I love you.
-And I'd go anywhere with you.
-Yeah.
You gonna leave him behind?
Sup?
Fuck it.
Let's go get our fucking money,
come on.
-You Brill?
-Who the fuck are you?
I'm nobody.
Funny,
I was just thinking that.
Yo, let's just fucking do
this, 'aight?
Check this shit out.
-Good, brother?
-Yeah, we good.
Yo, homie. You, uh...
you're a little light,
don't you think?
How do you figure?
That's five hundred K.
- I'm sure it is.
- That's thirty percent.
-Yes, it is.
-Yo, that's what we agreed to.
What the fuck did you just say?
It's the only fucking deal
on the table.
We didn't have no choice.
What, you didn't think you need
to run that by me first?
Do we have a problem?
Yeah, we got a fucking
problem, hold on.
If you about that action,
just say the word.
Yo, we're good!
Aight?
Everybody, just calm down.
You the smart White boy,
best get your bitch in line--
What the fuck did
you just say?
You heard what the fuck I said!
Yeah, fuck 'em.
Come on.
All right, okay, All right.
No, you're right,
it is what it is,
I apologize.
Hey... you...
Come on, you're gonna
miss the best part.
Yup. There you go.
What the fuck!
Go, go, go, go!
Oh, God.
I knew it. I fucking knew it.
Oh, shit!
All right. Get down.
All right.
Don't do anything stupid.
Yo, be cool. Mick.
Six, thirty six, C.
Drop it to me.
Yo, Nussy. Boss.
I don't know how
to tell you this.
-Tell me what?
-The meet went ugly.
Brill's gone.
What you mean "gone"?
Gone. White boys executed him.
Knocked off everyone.
Nah. Not everyone.
Nussy. Yo! Wait!
Let me explain.
Nah, I can't hear nothin'.
What?! 'How bout now?
Nah, still nothin'.
Wait, what? I don't get it.
'Cause if I could hear you,
you'd be an apparition.
A what?
A fucking ghost, nigga.
If I could hear you,
you'd be a motherfucking ghost.
At least that's what
you're gonna be
when Stitches
delivers you to me.
So I can feed you
to the fucking alligators.
Bitch ass nigger.
You heard that?
Yes, sir.
Look man, I'm tellin' you,
I ain't wanna help him.
Not one damn bit.
But I had no choice.
-He put a fucking Glock
to my head.
-A glock?
Yes, sir. Saw it written
right on the side.
Had a shiny pearl handle grip.
It--
Oh, yeah?
Did it have any engraving in it?
You know on that...
shiny pearl handle.
Yes, sir. Yeah, it did.
Had a grim reaper
carved in on it.
Really?
That sound like something
you lie about?
Then, they put the gun
in my mouth,
and pulled back the handle.
Wait, they put it in your mouth?
I thought you said
they put in to your head.
Look, he put it to my head,
then in my mouth.
All right? Then the crazy
son of a bitches start arguing
about which one's
gonna get to pull the trigger.
-Holy shit!
-Mmm!
Put it in your mouth,
and pulled it out...
Man, I swear for God,
can you believe that shit?
No.
No, I don't.
Who are you?
You ever heard
of the Pinocchio effect?
The pokey no fect?
No, no.
Pinocchio.
You know, the cute wooden puppet
that wished he was a real boy?
Every time he told a lie,
his nose would grow.
Man, I told you.
I swear for God.
What do I have to gain
from lying to you?
You see, Edwin...
Mind I call you Edwin?
You see...
The Pinocchio effect is
when someone's lying,
they know they're lying
So they're working
as hard as they can
to convince you,
that they ain't.
They start babbling,
and going on...
Start spitting out more details,
more words, than necessary.
You know, shit like,
'Do you think I'd lie
about something like that?'
Or, 'What do I have to gain,
lying to you all?'
Whoa.
Wait... what do you think
I'm lying about?
Everything.
For one, a Glock's
a polymer pistol. It's plastic.
You can't add grips to it.
Especially no pearl handle ones.
And, second, it's a striker
fire, hammerless--
Which means there's no hammer
to pull pack on, dumbass.
What the fuck is wrong with you,
you about to have a stroke
or something?
I have neither the time
nor the crayons
to explain all this to you.
But, I'm gonna give it a go,
anyway.
What you're unaware of is,
earlier this afternoon,
those crazy sons of bitches,
that you supplied the intel
and the boards to,
pulled a North Hollywood
shootout.
They murdered six officers
and put another
in critical condition.
Which makes you an accessory to,
at minimum...
Six counts of capital murder.
Now, you're realizing
the gravity of your situation.
All right, look. I had no
fucking idea, all right?
They were supposed to go in
on the prowl.
Break in the night before.
Look, I had no idea
they were gonna kill no one,
-all right?
-I'm sure the state of Louisiana
would really appreciate
that explanation.
Oh, fuck me.
Yeah, yeah, that's about right.
All right, look, look...
What can I do, all right?
Tell me, tell me...
What can I do?
Tell me 'bout your customers.
These guys that put you
in this hole.
Okay, it was, uh,
two White dudes.
I think they might've
been brothers.
How'd you come
to that conclusion?
They kept calling each other
bro and shit.
What are you, fucking Redman?
Who do you know in this city
who doesn't call each other bro?
It was different than that,
all right?
Look I just-- I feel like
they were brothers. All right?
-They kind of looked alike.
-Okay, okay.
This is good. Tell me more
about these brothers.
All right, uh, they, uh...
The younger one
was the smart one.
Okay? And--and...
The older one was the mean one.
What made the smarter one
smart?
He was just--
all about business.
He wanted
to know the details.
Very specific about the details.
And the mean one?
Oh, oh, he was bad news.
You know, some wild eyes.
He's the type of guy
that's lookin' for any excuse
to hurt someone.
All right? He told me,
if I ratted on him,
he'd find me,
and leave me twitchin'
in my own pile of shit.
And... he was...
very, very specific
about the pile of shit.
Okay. I believe you.
Keep going.
Okay... uh...
The smart one
had a Saint Jude pendant
around his neck.
And, uh...
the mean one had a...
Marine corps tattoo.
It said Semper Fi,
it had writin' on it.
What did the tattoo say?
It said Semper Fi somethin'
on the bottom,
-And, then, Sheridan somethin',
on top.
-Say what?
-It said Semper Fi
on the bottom.
-No no no... the name
Oh, uh, Sheridan Raid,
or something.
I remember 'cause of the tank.
Okay?
-That mean somethin' to you?
-One second--
So, should I have lawyer here,
or something?
Norma, look,
I need you to drop everything,
and run two names for me.
Listen. I understand how
and why you built the boards.
But, how did you know about
the Thursday deposits?
How did you know that branch
was temping
as a headquarter branch?
Look, I don't know nothing
about no headquarter branch
and no Thursday deposit either.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, send me that, right now.
-This them?
-Yeah yeah yeah.
Fuck yeah, that's them.
Look, that's the mean one,
and that's the smart one.
Hey, what's that mean,
what about... what about me?
Man, what the fuck, man,
we good?
Michael "Mick" Sheridan
and Jamie "James" Sheridan.
Irish White trash
from the Channel.
I popped Mick and his
younger brother years ago
in an agg assault,
they damn near killed a guy.
The brother walked,
but Mick got sent off to Angola
for seven years.
Both are ex-Marines
from the sandbox.
All right, get a bulletin
to all of our agencies.
-And get these photos
to the media ASAP.
-Copy.
-Any word on the bank employees?
-Not yet.
I'll rattle
Jean's cage again, though.
Follow up now.
-What happened?
-Mick happened.
That's what the fuck happened.
What is she talkin' about?
And, Jamie...
Why do you have all the money?
We had to move.
We had to dump it.
Do you have any idea
who that was?
That was Brill Waynes,
Nussy's brother.
- Nussy...
- We are so dead.
It's okay. We're fine.
Yo, we're better than fine.
Everybody's share
just got a serious fucking bump.
Where we at with the island?
Hey, the passports,
where we at?
What's the matter?
You're not gonna be happy
till we're all dead,
anyway, right?
- What?
- Look, I get it.
Mick, you've always wanted
a warrior's death.
I ain't afraid of dying, bro.
Yeah, no, no,
we all know.
If we do get out of this,
we go our separate ways.
We're never
gonna see each other again.
- Bro.
- Don't bro me.
You ain't thinkin' straight.
I've never been more clear
in my whole life.
Every pile of shit
I've ever stepped in
is because of you, Mick.
Who got you the money for Joan?
Who got you outta
hell in Providence?
How many beatings
I took for you from our old man?
You owe me.
No.
After tonight, the debt's paid.
Hey... Hey!
I'm your fucking brother!
What, that don't mean
nothin' to you?
This is about her, right?
You gonna let that fucking bitch
come between us?
Say that again.
What? Bitch?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Bro!
Stitches, baby!
I was just about to call you!
Two local men have been
identified as shooters
in today's brutal bank robbery.
Their names are
Michael Sheridan,
41 years of age,
and his brother,
James Sheridan, 35 years.
Both own extensive rap sheets.
Both men are former
United States Marines.
Having served deployments
in both Iraq and Afghanistan.
The FBI robbery task force unit
is said to be closing in
on them.
As we report to you
this evening.
All right, so I just
got off the line with Jean.
Something did pop.
One of those bank tellers,
that pretty brunette?
Ava Rishoto,
she grew up in Irish Channel
Now, she only had
a couple of dings
in her sealed juvie record.
-Such as?
-Petty theft at 13,
and a P.I. at 15.
Eh, there's more.
I told you Jean was digging.
So he pulls the bank accounts
on all of 'em.
And she's got over
75 grand in deposits.
Three weeks after they
pulled that job in Metairie.
-So, you followed the money?
-All digital.
Something called, uh,
Secret Angels.
It's one of those
anonymous sites
where you
crowdfund sad stories.
Now, all the money did go
to pay the hospital bills.
And nothing else
looks suspicious.
She's still carrying her house
and her car note.
But...
those dates matchin' up
like that, that just...
-makes for one hell
of a coincidence.
-Hey, Givens!
-What you workin'?
-You ain't heard?
- Heard what?
- Narcotics on the scene.
They've got six baggers
on the ground in Central City.
-Look's like it's Nussy's group.
-How do you figure?
Your boy Brill is one of 'em.
When'd this happen?
Shit, the bodies
ain't even cold yet.
I gotta roll.
What's a Brill?
Only the little brother
to the biggest gangsta
in the wards.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Big enough gangsta
to wash one point five mil?
He'll definitely
be on the list.
Where can we find this Nussy?
Well, he's got a club
over on Magazine.
Show me.
Jamie.
Jamie...
Jamie!
- Jamie!
- Yo, yo! Okay.
-Hey...
-Jamie!
- You okay?
- Jamie.
Bro?
Hey, yo, yo, you good?
You okay?
Jamie, fucking,
I'm so fucking sorry, bro.
Bro.
I'm so fucking sorry.
I got this, bro. I do.
I'm--I'm gonna tell 'em
it was me.
You just ain't gettin' it, man.
No matter what you say,
they're just gonna kill us,
anyway.
Ava!
Hey...
I'm so sorry.
Hey, bro.
It wasn't them.
It was me.
It was all me.
Is that right?
Hey,
there's more money than this,
A lot more money.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah. Just let her go.
-Yeah, this one?
-Yeah, even trade.
-Hey, hey--
-Come on, man--
Hey!
Even fuckin' trade, man.
A million cash,
I stashed it.
No, it ain't gonna happen.
Come on, what the fuck's
wrong with you?
-It's a million dollars.
-No, it ain't.
Brill already
told me what you left him.
That's all you got right there.
Plus, my boy Stitches
over there...
that motherfucker
got somethin' wicked
for her ass.
Hold on, princess.
Hey, yo, motherfucker,
it was me that dumped
your little bitch ass brother.
Oh, yeah.
You should've heard him.
Begged me. Whimpered.
Cried like
a little fucking bitch.
Until I jammed
that .45 in his mouth.
Hey, yo, homie.
You know anything
about the terminal effects
of contact shots?
No?
That's a big word.
You see,
with the terminal
effects of contact shots,
the body body absorbs
all the discharge
from the round.
Not just the fucking bullet.
All those gasses...
expanding that fucking fast?
Whoo!
That's some savage,
ugly shit, bro.
You gotta trust me on this one.
Your little brother Brill...
That's gonna be a closed casket.
Well, I smell
the vapors of hell on you, boy.
You good,
but you're not gonna play me.
No. I'm--I'mma savor the moment.
Got plans for you.
Take my time.
Make it a few nights, even.
See that container over there?
Know y'all been wondering
what that is, all night, huh?
That's a hundred gallons
of sulfuric acid.
Turn a man into soup in minutes.
Real wicked shit.
Yeah, I got that
from my Mexican friends.
They got it goin' on.
Hey, yo, Stitches.
Let's show these fools
a little demo real quick.
Get their fucking mind right.
I just want you to know
it's about to get real noisy
in here.
Real noisy.
No no no no no no.
God, god, no, please.
Wait, wait.
Jamie, Jamie, Jamie.
-Jamie, stop him--
-Hey, hey, come on, man.
Hey! Hey! There's more money--
-Jamie, stop him!
-Hey, look at me, man.
There's more
fuckin' money, man.
Jamie, stop him!
Jamie! Jamie!
You don't have to do this!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
No! No, no!
No! Fuckin' no!
-Ahh!
-Take that, motherfucker.
Take it. Take it like a champ!
You motherfucker!
I'm gonna fucking murder you!
That's what I'm talkin' bout!
Ooh-whee!
- This how you get
a party started!
You're gonna wish
you murdered me first.
So the Jet tells me,
that ya'll are brothers.
You the younger brother?
Am I wrong?
Hey, Stitches!
Let me have a go at it.
No, Mick, do something, Mick.
Do something.
Hey, hey! No, no, no, no.
No, don't do that!
No, no, no!
This is what you wanted, huh?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Shut the fuck up!
It's okay. It's okay.
Ah! Ah!
Okay, okay, you--
Talk about deja fucking vu.
Didn't I tell you,
you were gonna wish
you killed me first?
Don't you?
-Oh, you're all right.
-Come on!
We're gonna celebrate.
What?
Take her, take her and go.
Go! Go! Go!
All units,
we're receiving multiple calls
of 94s at 961 St. Mary Street.
Callers say,
it sounds like
automatic gunfire.
-That's Nussy's place.
Ten minutes away.
-Let's go!
-Freeze!
-Do what he says.
Put the gun down. Put it down!
-Not even for me, not for me.
-Put the gun down.
Come on, man,
you don't want to do this!
-Think about Joan--
-Put it down.
-Think about Joan, Jamie.
-Don't be stupid!
Now!
That's it! Slowly!
Good. Now step back.
Let me see your waistband.
Pull up your shirt.
Put 'em on the ground.
Kick 'em to me.
Ma'am, you back up,
till I say stop.
-Okay.
-Do what he says.
Back! Back!
-Stop!
-Uh, yes, sir.
You, to your knees!
To your knees!
- Six, 36, headquarters.
- Six, 36, go ahead.
I've got a White male.
I'm at the corner
of Laurel and Second Street.
The subject matches
the description
of one of the shooters
from the BOLO from the bank.
-That's blocks away.
-Come on Nico,
just get us there.
Go, just go.
You're gonna fry
for what you did today,
and I'm gonna
reserve a front row sea-
Wait!
What the hell?
Why'd you do that, bro?
Cause I love you, bro.
Look at me, look at me, Jamie,
look at me! Hey, hey!
Take cover!
Babe, we gotta go.
Come on, Jamie!
Come on!
Go. Let's go!
Runaways, shots fired,
suspect fleeing on foot.
1200 block.
Be advised, plainclothes
officers in pursuit.
Let's go!
FBI, six, 25.
Add us to the search.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Oh, my--
Jamie...
Yeah. Come on.
Gonna make the block.
Back door!
Move! Move!
I'm on Maura,
headed to Josephine,
I'm almost on you guys.
-Clear!
-Clear. Go go go!
To the gate!
What the fuck!
Get the fuck out of my house!
-FBI!
-Move, move! Stay down!
He's hit.
You got eyes on him?
-No, you?
-Negative.
I got eyes on him!
Nico, ya'll go right!
He's gotta be here somewhere.
Gunshot can't be far.
-Take left.
-All right. Head on a swivel.
I've got blood.
Fuck. Drop it.
Bad move, pal.
Back up, back the fuck up!
-Drop it, punk!
-Drop the gun!
-No!
-Take the shot, Mike!
Take it. Take the shot.
Yeah, Mikey, If you got a shot,
you should take it.
Take it!
Oh, fu--
Suspect down, suspect down.
Fuck, fuck.
Where's your brother?
He's dead. I...
He's fucking dead.
Dead.
Officers need an ambulance.
Tell Joan how much I love her,
okay? Every day.
-Every day.
I'm gonna take care of her.
I love you so much.
So fucking much.
I love you, too, Jamie.
I love you.
-What you lookin' for?
-Somebody went in here,
tryin' to find
ya'll teeth or something
I can ID him by
before he completely dissolves.
I recognize this glob of shit.
It's the one I tattooed
at the bank.
-You sure?
-Absolutely.
-So that only
leaves the brother.
-Sir...
You guys wanna
take a look at this?
Mean anything to you?
I guess that means
he wasn't lying.
-How'd that survive?
-Silver.
Noble metals
don't react to sulfuric acid.
Good afternoon, Mrs. Rishoto.
Do you remember me?
-Uh, Special Agent Ross.
-Yes! Are you all right?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
-Yeah.
Oh! I just...
I slipped on some water,
gettin' out the shower.
- Ouch!
- Yeah, yeah.
Do you mind if I come in?
I just have a few
follow-up questions for you.
-Yeah, Yeah. Sure.
-Yeah. Thank you.
What a beautiful baby!
Hey, hey!
So, how is she doing?
I heard that she
had a surgery recently.
Last spring.
She's doin' good.
Doctors say she's
probably gonna be fine.
Oh, that's good to hear.
A congenital heart disorder...
I heard that surgery
is very expensive
to cover all those costs...
We were blessed.
We crowdfunded,
and a lot of generous people
came to our rescue.
But you already knew that,
didn't you, Special Agent.
You just said "we".
We were blessed?
Yeah, that's right.
Me and my baby.
That was incredibly
generous.
And the donors?
They're all anonymous?
Yeah, that's how it works.
-People can really surprise you.
-And the father?
He's not around anymore.
He's gone.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Don't be. Some things
just aren't meant to be.
You know...
I... I have...
a little girl, too.
Well... not too little anymore.
-She's beautiful.
-Yeah, I think so, too.
But... she has
a sadness in her eyes.
You see it, too.
Yeah, that's on me.
You know, her mother and I...
were just a really bad match.
A bad match that caused
my daughter a lot of pain.
All I can do now is hope
that doesn't scar her too badly.
- Can I give you
a piece of advice?
You seem like a smart man,
a good man even.
But, there's somethin'
you ain't figured out yet.
- Really?
- Yeah...
My daddy, he spent a lifetime
lettin' me down.
But it don't matter,
'cause he still my daddy.
Every little girl needs one.
It's just how it is.
Yeah, it might take us
a while to figure that out,
but we always do.
And, really, your job...
is simple.
Do what you can
to own your shit.
Try to make up for it.
And just wait for her.
"Wait"?
Yeah. Wait. That's it.
Don't ever give up.
Is that what your father did?
Wait?
No. He didn't.
You said that the only option
you have was to
just hope your little girl
will be okay.
That ain't the way I see it.
You could just choose
to leave your ex
where she should
be, in the past.
And focus on starting over
with your daughter.
Hmm. You know...
that's really excellent advice.
It's been lovely chatting
with you, Special Agent Ross.
I hope you have a better day.
Good luck, Mrs. Rishoto.
Hey...
Thank you.
-How'd that go?
-It went.
And what about her?
Bad guys are dead.
All the money's recovered.
It's over.
Yeah, we could charge her,
absolutely ruin her.
And her daughter would probably
get put in the system.
I'll be in the car.
Hi.
It's a beautiful day.
I've got somebody
I want you to meet.
Somebody real special.
Come on.